Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Office File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 27-89)
  - Travel
    - Domestic
      - Trips
        - 1970
          - California, August 22-31
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 60: 20)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 60: 21)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 60: 22)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 60: 23)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 60: 24)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 60: 25)
            - Statements (Box-folder 60: 26)
          - Oregon, California, September 1-6
            - Executive orders (Box-folder 60: 27)
            - General (Box-folder 60: 28)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 60: 29)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 60: 30)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 60: 31)
            - Press releases (holograph notes) (Box-folder 60: 32)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 60: 33)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 60: 34)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 60: 35)
            - Statements (Box-folder 60: 36)
          - New York, Kansas, Illinois, September 16-17
            - General (Box-folder 60: 37)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 60: 38)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 60: 39)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 60: 40)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 60: 41)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 60: 42)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 60: 43)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 60: 44)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 60: 45)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 60: 46)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 60: 47)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 60: 48)
          - Georgia, Florida, October 8-12
            - General (Box-folder 61: 1)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 61: 2)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 61: 3)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 61: 4)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 61: 5)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 6)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 7)
          - Connecticut, October 12
            - General (Box-folder 61: 8)
            - Messages (Box-folder 61: 9)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 61: 10)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 11)
            - Statements (Box-folder 61: 12)
          - Vermont, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Wisconsin, October 17
            - General (Box-folder 61: 13)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 61: 14)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 15)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 16)
            - Statements (Box-folder 61: 17)
          - Ohio, North Dakota, North Carolina, Missouri, Tennessee, Indiana, October 19-20
            - General (Box-folder 61: 18)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 61: 19)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 61: 20)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 21)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 22)
            - Statements (Box-folder 61: 23)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 61: 24)
          - New York, October 23-24
            - General (Box-folder 61: 25)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 61: 26)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 61: 27)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 28)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 29)
          - Maryland, October 24
            - General (Box-folder 61: 30)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 31)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 32)
            - Statements (Box-folder 61: 33)
          - Florida, Texas, Illinois, Minnesota, Nebraska, Caliornia, October 27-30
            - General (Box-folder 61: 34)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 61: 35)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 61: 36)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 61: 37)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 61: 38)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 61: 39)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 61: 40)
            - Statements (Box-folder 61: 41)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 61: 42)
          - Arizona, New Mexico, Nevada, Utah, California, October 31
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 62: 1)
            - General (Box-folder 62: 2)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 62: 3)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 62: 4)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 5)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 62: 6)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 62: 7)
            - Statements (Box-folder 62: 8)
            - Telegrams (Box-folder 62: 9)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 62: 10)
          - California, November 1-4
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 62: 11)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 62: 12)
            - Statements (Box-folder 62: 13)
          - Florida, November 6-15
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 62: 14)
            - General (Box-folder 62: 15)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 62: 16)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 17)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 62: 18)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 62: 19)
            - Statements (Box-folder 62: 20)
          - Pennsylvania, remarks, November 17 (Box-folder 62: 21)
          - New York, December 4
            - General (Box-folder 62: 22)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 62: 23)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 62: 24)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 62: 25)
          - Maryland, December 17-18
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 26)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 62: 27)
        - 1971
          - California, January 4-13
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 62: 28)
            - Executive orders (Box-folder 62: 29)
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 62: 30)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 62: 31)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 62: 32)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 62: 33)
            - Statements (Box-folder 62: 34)
          - Nebraska, January 14
            - General (Box-folder 62: 35)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 36)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 62: 37)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 62: 38)
          - Georgia, January 23
            - General (Box-folder 62: 39)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 62: 40)
            - Remarks (draft included) (Box-folder 62: 41)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 62: 42)
          - Virgin Islands, January 29-February 1
            - General (Box-folder 62: 43)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 62: 44)
            - Messages (Box-folder 62: 45)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 46)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 62: 47)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 62: 48)
            - Statements (Box-folder 62: 49)
          - Florida, February 11-15
            - General (Box-folder 62: 50)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 62: 51)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 62: 52)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 62: 53)
          - Hawaii, pool reports, February 17 (Box-folder 63: 1)
          - Iowa, March 1
            - General (Box-folder 63: 2)
              Includes printed matter.
            - Meetings (Box-folder 63: 3)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 63: 4)
            - Messages (Box-folder 63: 5)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 63: 6)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 63: 7)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 63: 8)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 9)
          - New York, March 5
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 63: 10)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 11)
          - Virginia, March 11
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 63: 12)
            - General (Box-folder 63: 13)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 63: 14)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 63: 15)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 63: 16)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 17)
          - Rhode Island, March 12
            - General (Box-folder 63: 18)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 63: 19)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 63: 20)
            - Remarks (includes draft) (Box-folder 63: 21)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 22)
          - Florida, March 13-15
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 63: 23)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 63: 24)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 63: 25)
            - Statements (Box-folder 63: 26)
          - Kentucky, March 17
            - General (Box-folder 63: 27)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 63: 28)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 29)
          - New York, March 19
            - General (Box-folder 63: 30)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 63: 31)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 32)
          - California, March 26-April 5
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 63: 33)
            - Executive orders (Box-folder 63: 34)
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 63: 35)
            - General (Box-folder 63: 36)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 63: 37)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 63: 38)
            - Messages (Box-folder 63: 39)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 63: 40)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 63: 41)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 63: 42)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 63: 43)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 63: 44)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 63: 45)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 46)
            - Statements (Box-folder 63: 47)
          - Virginia, April 19
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 63: 48)
            - General (Box-folder 63: 49)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 63: 50)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 63: 51)
          - California, April 30-May 3
            - General (Box-folder 64: 1)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 2)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 64: 3)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 64: 4)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 64: 5)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 64: 6)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 64: 7)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 8)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 9)
          - New Jersey, May 10
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 64: 10)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 11)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 64: 12)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 13)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 14)
          - Florida, May 15-17
            - General (Box-folder 64: 15)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 64: 16)
            - Statements (Box-folder 64: 17)
          - Florida, Texas, Alabama, May 22-25
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 64: 18)
            - General (Box-folder 64: 19)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 64: 20)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 21)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 64: 22)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 64: 23)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 64: 24)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 64: 25)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 64: 26)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 27)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 28)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 64: 29)
          - New York, May 26
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 64: 30)
            - General (Box-folder 64: 31)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 32)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 64: 33)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 64: 34)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 35)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 36)
          - Oklahoma, June 5
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 64: 37)
            - General (Box-folder 64: 38)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 39)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 40)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 41)
          - New York, Florida, June 18-21
            - General (Box-folder 64: 42)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 64: 43)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 64: 44)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 64: 45)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 64: 46)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 64: 47)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 64: 48)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 64: 49)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 64: 50)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 64: 51)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 64: 52)
          - New Jersey, June 22
            - General (Box-folder 65: 1)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 65: 2)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 65: 3)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 65: 4)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 65: 5)
          - Indiana, Illinois, June 24-25
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 65: 6)
            - General (Box-folder 65: 7)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 65: 8)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 65: 9)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 65: 10)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 65: 11)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 65: 12)
          - Missouri, California, July 6-9
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 65: 13)
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 65: 14)
            - General (Box-folder 65: 15)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 65: 16)
            - Press briefings (Box-folder 65: 17)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 65: 18)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 65: 19)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 65: 20)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 65: 21)
            - Statements (Box-folder 65: 22)
          - California, July 10-17
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 65: 23)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 65: 24)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 65: 25)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 65: 26)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 65: 27)
            - Statements (Box-folder 65: 28)
          - Ohio, Iowa, California, July 30-August 2
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 65: 29)
            - General (Box-folder 65: 30)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 65: 31)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 65: 32)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 65: 33)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 65: 34)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 65: 35)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 65: 36)
          - New Hampshire, Maine, August 6-8
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 66: 1)
            - General (Box-folder 66: 2)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 66: 3)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 66: 4)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 66: 5)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 66: 6)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 66: 7)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 66: 8)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 66: 9)
            - Statements (Box-folder 66: 10)
          - Maryland, general, August 13 (Box-folder 66: 11)
          - New York, Illinois, Wyoming, Texas, Idaho, August 17-19
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 66: 12)
            - General (Box-folder 66: 13)
            - Meetings (Box-folder 66: 14)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 66: 15)
            - Miscellaneous (holograph) (Box-folder 66: 16)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 66: 17)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 66: 18)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 66: 19)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 66: 20)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 66: 21)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 66: 22)
            - Statements (Box-folder 66: 23)
          - California, Ohio, Illinois, August 20-September 3
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 66: 24)
            - General (Box-folder 66: 25)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 66: 26)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 66: 27)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 66: 28)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 66: 29)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 66: 30)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 66: 31)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 66: 32)
            - Reports (Box-folder 66: 33)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 66: 34)
            - Statements (Box-folder 66: 35)
          - Maryland, remarks, September 5-6 (Box-folder 66: 36)
          - Michigan, Montana, Oregon, Washington, Alaska, September 23-27
            - General
              - General (Box-folder 67: 1)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 2)
              - Pool reports (Box-folder 67: 3)
              - Press kits (Box-folder 67: 4)
              - Press briefings (Box-folder 67: 5)
              - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 6)
            - Michigan
              - General (Box-folder 67: 7)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 8)
              - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 67: 9)
              - Press releases (Box-folder 67: 10)
              - Reports (Box-folder 67: 11)
              - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 12)
            - Montana
              - Fact sheets (Box-folder 67: 13)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 14)
              - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 67: 15)
              - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 16)
              - Statements (Box-folder 67: 17)
            - Oregon
              - Correspondence (Box-folder 67: 18)
              - Fact sheets (Box-folder 67: 19)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 20)
              - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 67: 21)
              - Press briefings (Box-folder 67: 22)
              - Press releases (Box-folder 67: 23)
              - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 24)
              - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 25)
              - Statements (includes drafts) (Box-folder 67: 26)
            - Washington
              - Correspondence (Box-folder 67: 27)
              - Fact sheets (Box-folder 67: 28)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 29)
              - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 67: 30)
              - Press briefings (Box-folder 67: 31)
              - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 32)
              - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 33)
              - Statements (Box-folder 67: 34)
            - Alaska
              - Correspondence (Box-folder 67: 35)
              - Fact sheets (Box-folder 67: 36)
              - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 37)
              - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 67: 38)
              - News summaries (Box-folder 67: 39)
              - Pool reports (Box-folder 67: 40)
              - Press briefings (Box-folder 67: 41)
              - Press releases (Box-folder 67: 42)
              - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 43)
              - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 44)
              - Statements (Box-folder 67: 45)
          - Florida, September 30-October 4
            - General (Box-folder 67: 46)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 47)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 67: 48)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 49)
            - Statements (Box-folder 67: 50)
          - West Virginia, October 8
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 67: 51)
            - General (Box-folder 67: 52)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 67: 53)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 67: 54)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 67: 55)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 67: 56)
            - Statements (Box-folder 67: 57)
          - North Carolina, October 15
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 68: 1)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 2)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 68: 3)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 68: 4)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 5)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 68: 6)
          - Maryland, October 18
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 68: 7)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 8)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 68: 9)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 10)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 68: 11)
            - Statements (Box-folder 68: 12)
          - Maryland, remarks, October 24 (Box-folder 68: 13)
          - Florida, New York, Illinois, November 5-10
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 68: 14)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 15)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 68: 16)
            - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 68: 17)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 68: 18)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 68: 19)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 68: 20)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 68: 21)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 68: 22)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 23)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 68: 24)
            - Statements (Box-folder 68: 25)
          - Florida, Ohio, November 18-22
            - General (Box-folder 68: 26)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 68: 27)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 68: 28)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 29)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 68: 30)
            - Statements (Box-folder 68: 31)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 68: 32)
          - Virginia, remarks, November 23 (Box-folder 68: 33)
          - California, November 25-29
            - Correspondence (Box-folder 68: 34)
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 68: 35)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 36)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 68: 37)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 68: 38)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 68: 39)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 40)
            - Statements (Box-folder 68: 41)
            - Telephone calls (Box-folder 68: 42)
          - Washington, D.C., Illinois, December 1
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 68: 43)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 44)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 68: 45)
            - News summaries (Box-folder 68: 46)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 68: 47)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 68: 48)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 68: 49)
          - Florida, December 2-6
            - Executive orders (Box-folder 68: 50)
            - General (Box-folder 68: 51)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 68: 52)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 68: 53)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 68: 54)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 68: 55)
          - Florida, December 15-18
            - General (Box-folder 69: 1)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 69: 2)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 3)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 4)
            - Statements (Box-folder 69: 5)
          - New York, schedules, December 18-19 (Box-folder 69: 6)
          - Florida, December 23-29
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 69: 7)
            - General (Box-folder 69: 8)
            - Pool reports (Box-folder 69: 9)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 10)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 11)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 69: 12)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 69: 13)
            - Statements (Box-folder 69: 14)
            - Television news reports (Box-folder 69: 15)
        - 1972
          - California, January 4-8
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 69: 16)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 17)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 18)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 69: 19)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 69: 20)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 69: 21)
            - Statements (Box-folder 69: 22)
          - Florida, January 21
            - Messages (Box-folder 69: 23)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 24)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 25)
          - Florida, February 4-12
            - General (Box-folder 69: 26)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 27)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 28)
            - Proclamations (Box-folder 69: 29)
            - Statements (Box-folder 69: 30)
          - Florida, March 2-3
            - Executive orders (Box-folder 69: 31)
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 69: 32)
            - Memoranda (Box-folder 69: 33)
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 34)
            - Press releases (Box-folder 69: 35)
            - Statements (Box-folder 69: 36)
          - Alabama, remarks, March 9 (Box-folder 69: 37)
          - Maryland, general, March 15 (Box-folder 69: 38)
          - New York, March 20
            - Fact sheets (Box-folder 69: 39)
            - Remarks (Box-folder 69: 40)
            - Schedules (Box-folder 69: 41)
          - Pennsylvania, Florida, April 6-8
            - Press conferences (Box-folder 69: 42)